Bokeh is a drama, science fiction, thriller film directed by Andrew Sullivan.
On a romantic getaway to Iceland, a young American couple wake up one
morning to discover every person on Earth has disappeared.
Their struggle to survive and to reconcile the mysterious event lead them to
reconsider everything they know about themselves and the world.
Jenai, played by Maika Monroe.
Riley, played by Matt O'Leary.
Nils, played by Arnar Jónsson.
Ivar, played by Gunnar Helgason.
Tour Guide, played by Berglind Rós Sigurôardóttir.
Bokeh is a 2017 science fiction drama film written and
directed by Geoffrey Orthwein and Andrew Sullivan.
It stars Maika Monroe and Matt O'Leary as two American tourists in Iceland who
find everyone else on the island has mysteriously vanished.
It premiered at the Santa Barbara International Film Festival and was
released theatrically in the United States on March 24, 2017.
The tone is emotional and thought_provoking and intense.